McKelvey, Jean T. Papers /3001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Other Publications; Photos, Certificates, Awards, etc. (Box 140)
  - McKelvey - VHS Tapes, 1991 (Box 140, Folder 60)
    2 VHs Tapes
- Confidential material removed from Box 5. (Box 141)